import { Question } from "../App";

export const oknotokData: Question[] = [
    {
        "question": "What is the profession of the main female character, Moon Gang-tae?",
        "options": ["Children’s book author", "Psychiatric nurse", "Artist", "Teacher"],
        "answer": "Children’s book author"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mental health condition does Moon Gang-tae's brother, Moon Sang-tae, have?",
        "options": ["Autism Spectrum Disorder", "Depression", "Bipolar Disorder", "Anxiety Disorder"],
        "answer": "Autism Spectrum Disorder"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the psychiatric hospital where much of the story takes place?",
        "options": ["OK Psychiatric Hospital", "Healing Garden", "Happy Life Clinic", "Sunshine Mental Health Center"],
        "answer": "OK Psychiatric Hospital"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main male lead in the series, who is also a caregiver and works in the psychiatric hospital?",
        "options": ["Moon Gang-tae", "Kim Soo-hyun", "Oh Ji-ho", "Lee Joon-gi"],
        "answer": "Moon Gang-tae"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the main female lead, who is also a famous writer with a troubled past?",
        "options": ["Ko Moon-young", "Kim Ji-won", "Choi Ji-eun", "Yoon Ji-woo"],
        "answer": "Ko Moon-young"
    },
    {
        "question": "What traumatic event from her past significantly affects Ko Moon-young's behavior and relationships?",
        "options": ["Abuse", "Neglect", "Family tragedy", "Bullying"],
        "answer": "Family tragedy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the title of Ko Moon-young’s bestselling book?",
        "options": ["The Wonderful Wizard", "The King’s Ransom", "The Prisoner of Love", "The Kingdom of Dreams"],
        "answer": "The Kingdom of Dreams"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who helps Ko Moon-young deal with her traumatic past and complex emotions?",
        "options": ["Moon Gang-tae", "Moon Sang-tae", "Dr. Oh Jung-se", "Dr. Lee"],
        "answer": "Moon Gang-tae"
    },
    {
        "question": "What unique feature does the character Moon Sang-tae have that is central to his role in the story?",
        "options": ["He is an illustrator", "He has a special talent", "He is a well-known actor", "He has a fear of butterflies"],
        "answer": "He has a fear of butterflies"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the central message of the series regarding mental health and healing?",
        "options": ["Acceptance and understanding", "Isolation and self-reliance", "Overcoming trauma through success", "Avoiding professional help"],
        "answer": "Acceptance and understanding"
    }
]
